Hey, I might have got some inside info
to ask this question here. Uh, what was
the hardest thing you did training
growing up as a kid? [laughter]
>> Uh, probably run run heels. That was
pretty hard. My dad used to since I was
like 9 years old just used to make us
get up at 6:00 in the morning and go run
heels. Also, like one time he made us
run like 20ome 200s on the track. So,
that was pretty hard with steel toe
boots. So, yeah, that was pretty hard.
When coach Harbaugh was describing you,
he used the term pitbull. Like is how
much is that where you got it from?
>> Yeah. Um, shoot. Yeah, I definitely got
it from that for sure. Um, I would say
pitbull. Like pit bull is a great word.
You know what I'm saying? Pit bull. I
would say I'm more like a Kane Corso
though. Like, you know what I'm saying?
Bigger dog. You know what I'm saying?
But yeah, I'm I'm ecstatic with that,
you know, uh, comparison for sure.
>> Can I ask, do you have a green Corsa?
you know?
>> No, I don't have any, but I'm I'm
planning to get one. You know, my
parents don't really like pets, so um I
never had one growing up, but you know
what I'm saying? If I'm living by
myself, you know, I might get a I might
get me a Kane Corso for sure.
>> What's the last uh 12 or so hours been
like for you since you've been dropped?
>> Um kind of feels unreal still to this
day. Like I'm in the New York Giants
facility. Like it's kind of crazy, but
um you know, I'm just happy to be here.
You know, I'm ready to go to work.
Honestly, if we could practice tomorrow,
I'll throw my cleat on right now. So,
>> what are your strengths as a player?
>> My strengths, I would say just my
competitive nature, you know. Um, and I
would say also like just my press man
ability. Um, I don't think there's, you
know, too many people in the draft. I
mean, not not too many people. There's
no one in the draft that's as good as me
as when it comes to press. And then, you
know, I I just want to continue to build
on that and, you know, continue to build
on my game, you know, so when the
seasons comes, I can, you know, be out
be dominant. So,
>> how much have they told you about that
press man appeal to them and what
they're going to do with this defense?
Um, yeah, they they've told me that, you
know, that was one of the biggest things
that they they liked about me. Just told
me about told me about, you know, just
my technique and, you know, how they
like my technique and, you know, not to
change it. You know what I'm saying? To
come in and continue to work on it and
continue to master it. So,
>> who have you modeled your game after?
Who are some of the players you hooked
up to?
>> Yeah. Um, so my uncle played um 10 years
in the league and, you know, he trained
Patrick Peterson when he was with the
Arizona Cardinals. So, yeah, Pat P is a
big one. and someone I've looked up to
since I was 13, 14 years old. Somebody
who I always watched. Um I would also
say um shoot Passer 10, Dell Rivas, JC
Horn, all those guys are, you know,
great great um manto man lock down
corners and they also get go get the
ball. So those are I guess some of the
main guys. You
>> mentioned Uncle Ro, obviously Coach Aral
mentioned you coached him and you told
us that, [clears throat] you know, he
kind of prepared you what to expect, but
what what have you learned from Mr.
Uncle Rod just from your development?
and just learning about how to be a pro,
how to be a football player.
>> Yeah, I I I learned everything from him
like him and my dad just about football
and then my uncle to the more technical
side of just playing the position,
playing corner. Um he taught me almost
everything I know about it. So, you
know, definitely um somebody I look up
to, somebody who I still go to to this
day, you know, if I need any advice
about the position. So,
>> when did you uh come up with the
celebration?
>> Uh I came up with it actually in the
spur. It was actually in the spur of the
moment. So like right right before you
know uh my first PU the season I was
like you know actually the night before
me and my roommate Tyman we were talking
about like celebrations we were going to
do and I was just trying to think of a s
and I was like bro I want to do
something that nobody else has done or
that you know nobody else is doing you
know. So um and in the spur of the
moment I thought of that cuz my last
name's hood. So and it kind of stuck.
So,
>> we'll take a few more. Harbaugh said he
thinks he would likely [clears throat]
fire in the corner.
>> How do you balance like being a rookie
and assimilating with trying to take a
job and and be a leader right away?
>> Yeah. Um, honestly, I'm just going to be
myself, you know. I'm not going to go in
there and try to step on anybody's toes,
but I am coming in there to compete, you
know, and um, if you know, that's just
that's just who I am. That's the type of
person I am. But I'm going to be myself.
I'm be fine, lighthearted. you know what
I'm saying? Not somebody who's always,
you know, I guess super serious, but you
know, I'm about my business and, you
know, I'mma come in there and compete.
So,
>> saw a couple times they put the video
out of your phone call, you got pretty
emotional. Sounded like you were still a
little emotional when you talked to us
last night. How do you manifest the
emotions or at least describe what it's
all about? Is it all the same or are
there different points where you just
feel it coming and say, you know what,
let it go?
>> Yeah. Um I I like I didn't have a choice
of whether I could hold it in or not.
I've been holding it in this whole
process cuz I mean I've been dreaming
about this since I was 6 years old. Like
looking at my ceiling dream about
playing in NFL and then to get to play
for such a story franchise as the Giants
and this great city of New York is just
you know something that you know I even
I couldn't have dreamed of. So, just
being able to be here in this moment is,
you know, amazing and definitely
something that, you know, I'm grateful
for and I'm going to uh be appreciative
of.
>> Are there any are there any wide
receivers that you have watched, you
know, I'm sure you watch a lot of
football and now you're thinking, "Oh, I
can get to cover him now."
>> Um, yeah. Like, I mean, shoot, I I was
um I'm a big football fan, you You know,
I'm a big fan of Jamar Chase, big fan of
Justin Jefferson, big fan of all the top
guys, Jason, Puka, Nakua, all the top
guys I'm a big fan of. So, you know,
being able to go out there and compete
with those guys is definitely a blessing
and something that, you know, I'm
looking forward to.
>> You mentioned story history of the
Giants. Is there any players like
particularly familiar with or era?
>> Yeah, I mean, you want me to name them
all?
Um,
>> Michael Strahan, Eli Manning, Odell
Beckham, [snorts] um, Lawrence Taylor,
just I mean like there's so many players
that, you know, I've come here, did the
right thing, and, you know, the city
loves them for it. So, um, yeah, I mean,
I'm a football guy. Like, I'm big on
football. It's all I know. It's all I
do. So, um, yeah, I mean, I love this
franchise and, you know, I'm glad to be
a part of it.